<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>eCOTS 2016 Regional Conference, Georgetown KY</title>
 <link href="https://homerhanumat.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="https://homerhanumat.github.io/"/>
 <updated>2016-01-24T13:13:10-05:00</updated>
 <id>https://homerhanumat.github.io</id>
 <author>
   <name>Homer White</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Announcing the eCOTS 2016 Regional Conference at Georgetown</title>
   <link href="https://homerhanumat.github.io/2016/01/23/ecots16-regional-georgetown-announcement.html"/>
   <updated>2016-01-23T15:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>https://homerhanumat.github.io/2016/01/23/ecots16-regional-georgetown-announcement</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-conference&quot;&gt;The Conference&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are happy to announce the eECOTS 2016 Regional Conference at Georgetown (&lt;strong&gt;eCOTS16-RCG&lt;/strong&gt;).  This is a one-day gathering to enhance &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.causeweb.org/ecots/ecots16/&quot;&gt;eCOTS 2016&lt;/a&gt;, the biennial electronic meeting of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.causeweb.org/uscots/&quot;&gt;USCOTS&lt;/a&gt;, the United States Conference on the Teaching of Statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;eCOTS16-RCG&lt;/strong&gt; is set for May 20, 2016 on the campus of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.georgetowncollege.edu/&quot;&gt;Georgetown College&lt;/a&gt; in Central Kentucky.  The conference receives sponsorship from eCOTS 2016.  Participants should register for eCOTS prior to registering for &lt;strong&gt;eCOTS16-RCG&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Toggle the sidebar for more information, including:  registration instructions, conference schedule, etc.  Note especially the Comments and Discussion link.  This takes you to the Issues page for the GitHub repository for this website.  If you sign up for a GitHub account (free!) then you can post questions and initiate discussion threads.  This will be useful in a variety of ways, from ride-sharing arrangements to preliminary discussions of contributed presentations.  Click the “Watch” button on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/homerhanumat/ecots16ky&quot;&gt;repository itself&lt;/a&gt; in order to receive email notifications of all discussions.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
